March 7th, 2026.
The rehearsal for the under live was also in the middle of the day.
A new song was being played.
The title of this under song is,
I envy love.
The song is bright and up-tempo,
and the nuances were important in the choreography.
If you do it too fast, the silhouette will be blurry.
Please show me a little bit of this and this hand.
It doesn't go like this.
The hand remains a little here.
If you do it like this, you'll feel hungry.
Please do it so that your fingertips are facing down.
Seniors who recommend the choreography with fun.
The 6th grade students have no room for that.
It's over here.
The rehearsal is over.
Thank you very much.
The 6th grade students are about to start practicing.
On the spot, there was a figure of Okamoto and Iwamoto practicing together.
It's over.
You should sleep.
But you should sleep.
You'll remember it when you sleep.
Sleep one more time.
You're smiling.
I'm worried.
You don't have anything tomorrow, right?
It's okay.
In the morning?
Until then.
Let's go to sleep.
I know that you're coming with all your might.
I can only help you.
You're over the cap.
I don't know what will be the purpose of the 6th grade students.
There are a lot of things I don't know.
But I have to get over it.
I want to pamper them.
I think it's different to pamper them all.
But in the end, I'll say, are you okay?
I can say it because I'm doing my best.
I can do it gently.
I have to say what I should say and what I shouldn't say.
There is also a conflict between seniors and seniors.
The balance of kindness and strictness that the surroundings think of.
What about the 6th grade students, Suzuki?
Every time I see my seniors' performances, I get anxious.
6th grade students are in there.
I haven't been able to remember the moves.
I feel like I'm bothering them.
I wonder if the seniors are in the right place in what they can make.
I'm anxious about that.
I'm still not at the stage of expressing myself.
A week before the live performance, the first rehearsal.
With the same movement as the live performance,
all the members and all the staff will check the current state.
Until the start time, they will check their anxiety.
At 16 o'clock, the investment rehearsal begins.
It's time.
As the rehearsal progressed, all the staff noticed something.
The seniors are in a bad mood.
Of course, I'm a 6th grader.
When I looked at the rehearsal after the live performance,
it was clear that the seniors were more anxious.
The seniors were more anxious.
That's what I felt when I first saw it.
If you do a live rehearsal seriously,
you'll sweat a lot and you'll run out of breath.
That's why I'm not good enough as a 6th grader.
I haven't been able to breathe that much.
I want to be responsible for my performance and my singing.
If I try to do it with all my strength,
I can't make a cool face at all.
I had to look more and more stupid.
I think it's still the stage where I'm going to fill it up.
In order to keep going that far,
I have to put in more and more choreography,
my own singing, lyrics,
until they come out unconsciously.
The seniors are already doing that,
so when it's time,
they can show their power at once.
I'm still a 6th grader, of course,
but I can't breathe that much.
I have no choice but to do it.
The attitude towards the rehearsal.
The desire to do it.
I know that the 6th grader is having a hard time.
Even so, the performance in front of people
was one step ahead of what they could do.
The strict words from the staff.
On the other hand,
what about the other girls?
This time, I was too desperate to keep up with each song,
so I put in more and more thoughts
If I perform,
I want to be able to perform.
I think I need time to analyze each song.
What I've done for this year-end rehearsal
is what I've done today.
If I think about it,
I really have to live for these three days
because I don't want to regret it.
If today's rehearsal
was the real thing,
the people who like me now
I thought that
if it was today's performance,
I wouldn't like it anymore.
On that day,
I wanted to be able to perform
to make people want to see this girl.
For the remaining week,
I thought about the meaning of being here
and I'm going to live for a week
for the under-live.
What's the point of repeating this?
I'll think about it again
and I'll think about how I'll spend this period
with the feeling of going to the live.
I'm angry or I'm not doing it.
It's not like I'm angry.
I want everyone to see it more because everyone is doing it.
So I wonder if it's like this.
I don't want you to think that I'm bad, but if you tell me that, I'm sure you'll tell me.
I don't know if it's like that, but I think it's okay for us to hear it, or for adults to hear it.
I'll do my best, because it's the kids who say it.
I think it's good, but I think it's better to look at it when you don't have a mirror.
I have a solid image, so if I can do it, I think it would be better to do it without a mirror when I go to the main venue.
I can't do it, but it's hard to do it, so I want to solve it with this.
I think we need to work harder for our 6th grade.
I think we can still do it.
I think it's a good thing.
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm sure I can do it.
I think I didn't do it well, so I'm very disappointed.
This important under-live, if I say it as it is, I think it would have ruined the atmosphere and goodness of the under-live.
But I'm very grateful that you talked to us like that.
I want to do my best.
March 2026.
Nogizaka 46.
41st single under-live.
I have to go down by myself.
I can't see a different view.
I have to keep looking to see what else it is.
Documentary of 41 single stress Under Live
Different scenery from 6th generation